Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Stop dilly-dallying. Big Brother.
This yard sale isn't gonna set up itself.
Coming. Sally.
I love a spring yard sale.
It's the perfect time
to get rid of all your old stuff
to make room for new stuff.
I'll be sad to see
some of these old things go.
Hopefully. they'll make
someone else just as happy.
Well. all the money we get
will make me happy.
Snoopy. do you have anything
you'd like to sell?
What can a dog have to sell
at a yard sale?
Is that my hockey stick?
I prefer a more curated approach.
It's all about the presentation.
Wow. there sure is
some great stuff in here.
My old glove.
I know it doesn't fit anymore.
but it's full of memories.
I almost made a game-winning catch
with this glove.
So. it's really just a game-losing glove.
We're open for business.
Right this way.
No pushing. no shoving.
-There's plenty for everyone.
-Look. check it out!
Classic Bunny Wunny.
Nothing says spring like a new perfume.
Wouldn't you agree. my Sweet Babboo?
I'm not your Sweet Babboo.
but I do love a fresh scent.
What does it smell like?
No idea. My mom donated them.
This one is called. "Sample."
It's pronounced "Sample." It's French.
Do I detect a top note of jasmine?
-Or is that…
-It's bubble gum. you blockhead.
I'll take it.
What else do you have?
Vanilla pudding. rose bouquet. strawberry…
I'll take them all.
How much for this fishing pole. Sally?
That's $1.35. Franklin.
My grandpa always says.
"You can't put a price
on a good day of fishing."
How about a $1.20?
Sold.
Fifty cents?
What am I? A millionaire?
Hey. Snoopy. Does this accordion work?
No. thanks.
My mom would just make me practice.
Have it. Don't need it. Don't want it.
Nope. Never.
A waffle maker?
I'm more of a pancake gal.
Who painted this? A dog?
I never realized
beagles were so sensitive.
How much for this baseball card. Chuck?
That one?
I didn't realize I put it in there.
I should probably keep it.
Peppermint Patty.
It's my favorite.
How about this one?
That's my other favorite.
What about this ball?
It looks like it's never even been hit.
Actually. they're all my favorites.
You sure have a funny way
of doing business. Chuck.
Hey. Charles.
Is all this baseball gear really for sale?
Hi. Milo.
Funny you should mention that.
Because my baseball team.
we're called The Goose Eggs.
on account of how...
You've never scored a run.
I remember.
I know how that feels.
Maybe all you need
is a little more practice.
It's kind of hard.
Austin lost our only bat.
And Ruby still uses
an oven mitt for a glove.
This would be a major step up
for the team.
How much?
It's just…
These are for display… only.
It did seem too good to be true.
Charlie Brown. you're the only kid I know
who could have a yard sale
and not sell anything!
That'll be ten cents.
It served its purpose.
Attention. shoppers. everything must go.
No reasonable offer refused.
Nice!
Yes!
Thank you. All sales final.
Thanks. All sales final.
Pleasure doing business with you.
All sales final!
You sold everything.
Even the tables.
I made a pretty penny too.
I even sold an old dollhouse.
I forgot I had an old dollhouse.
Sally. you sold Snoopy's doghouse?
Are you certain?
I'm pretty sure I heard dollhouse.
Do you remember who you sold it to?
It's kinda hard to think
with all that noise.
Sally! It's important.
I don't remember.
In the thrill of commerce.
it's all a blur.
Poor Snoopy.
People think that a lot could be said
Welcome to your new home. Snoopy.
About where it is you lay your head
A big old house or a tin-roof shed
But home is where your heart can rest
Chandeliers or velvet drapes
A big old table
And some porcelain plates
I don't care how you fill your space
You ain't home
Until your heart feels safe
All of these memories
To share with my friends
Warm autumn mornings or wintery winds
Life is full of the stories we write
Home's not a house
It's a feeling inside
Some say it's over the rainbow
Deep inside of your dreams
Deep inside your dreams
But lucky for me
I'm where I'm supposed to be
Home where your heart found me
Riding bikes or hide and seek
Well. it all means more
When you're here with me
There's so many stories yet to be
Oh. home is where your heart is free
Some say it's over the rainbow
Deep inside of your dreams
Deep inside your dreams
But lucky for me
I'm where I'm supposed to be
Home where your heart found me
Well. it is spring.
Think of it as the perfect time
for a fresh start.
Why don't we just go shopping
for a new doghouse?
Don't worry. Snoopy.
I'm sure we'll find something
you like in here.
This store sells just about everything.
Here they are.
This one looks cozy.
This one's festive.
How about this one? It floats.
Too cold.
Maybe too contemporary.
I'm surprised they can even
call this one a house.
I'm sorry we couldn't find you
a new doghouse. Snoopy.
If only we could figure out where it went.
It's a real mystery.
The real mystery is
why can't I have a normal dog?
The world's greatest detective
is on the case.
Ninety-eight. 99. 100.
That's a personal best. sir.
Yes!
Sorry. Peppermint Patty.
Snoopy thought you were a typewriter.
I can never quite figure you out. Chuck.
All hail the bubble king!
Is that the scent of freshly baked
chocolate chip cookies?
Save me one. Snoopy.
Your Majesty.
Watch it. beagle!
What is the meaning of this?
He's following the scent
of chocolate chip cookies.
You must mean my new perfume.
I got it at your yard sale.
Take a sniff.
Yep. freshly baked chocolate chip cookies.
I've been licked by a dog!
Get the iodine. Call animal services.
Germs. germs. germs!
At least it turned out to be a nice day.
Sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
It hasn't been a nice day for you.
Maybe it would help to think
of something else. like baseball.
That always makes me feel better.
I imagine pitching a perfect game
or catching a fly ball.
Or sliding into home.
Did I say home?
I can't say anything right.
Snoopy. I know your doghouse
means the world to you.
We're going to get it back
no matter how long it takes.
All spring.
Into summer. fall. winter. night. day.
Even recess.
Just remember. we're in this together.
Snoopy. wait.
Let's not jump to any conclusions.
Hello. Charles.
Milo? Earlier today
you were at our yard sale.
That was a very good yard sale. Charles.
Thank you. Milo.
Did you happen to buy anything?
I sure did.
I got a whole box of stuff.
I bought some comic books
and a jigsaw puzzle and a bicycle horn.
I bought some macaroni art.
Two hair bows for Ruby.
They were buy one get one free.
Let's see. What else?
What about a doghouse?
Or a dollhouse.
Did you happen to buy either of those
from my sister Sally?
No.
But I did get something much better.
It's the Goose Eggs'
official new clubhouse!
Hey!
Do you want a tour?
I love this place!
The thing is. this is Snoopy's doghouse.
It is?
Sally wasn't supposed to sell it.
It was a mistake.
Do you think there's any way
I could get it back?
Are you kidding me?
Look at the Goose Eggs.
This clubhouse is the best thing
that ever happened to us.
Plus. I have a receipt from your sister.
-I want to live here forever.
-"All sales final."
Please. Milo.
There must be something I can do.
Sorry. Charles.
It wouldn't be fair to the team.
Everything okay. Charlie Brown?
I'm afraid not. Franklin.
It's Snoopy. We lost his doghouse.
You had me worried there.
What do you mean?
Don't get me wrong. it's a big deal.
But it's not the end of the world.
I'm not sure Snoopy would agree.
Houses are important.
but they're made
from wood. nails and bricks.
Also concrete. stone. a variety of metals…
The point is.
those things are all replaceable.
Whenever I've moved houses.
I found the important things
always have a way of coming with me.
My memories. my family.
That's what home is to me. Charlie Brown.
You just need to know
what's worth holding on to.
-Everything else is just…
-Stuff.
Good advice.
Did your grandpa tell you that?
I read it on the back of a cereal box.
Thanks. Franklin.
Hey. I knew that was
around here somewhere.
Let me know
if you catch a set of encyclopedias.
Fifty-six. 57…
Who knew spring-cleaning could be so fun?
And profitable.
Now remember.
always count the quarters first
because they're the easiest to stack.
Wow.
Are you sure you want to
give all this up. Charles?
I'm not sure of a lot of things. Milo.
But I know there's nothing
I wouldn't give up for my dog.
Do we have a deal?
Deal.
I hope the Goose Eggs
have as much fun with it as I did.
Dibs on the bat.
-This glove has fingers.
-Hooray!
Perfect fit.
Play ball.
Almost.
Go long. Leland.
I got it. I got it.
I almost got it.
Hooray. Yay.
Big leagues. here we come.
Nice to see your house
back where it belongs.
With a few fixes. it'll be as good as new.
I'm so sorry. Snoopy.
But there's nothing here
we can't repair or replace.
A home is made
from the memories you create
and the people you love.
And no matter how many times
you lose your house.
you'll always have a home with me.
old pal.
And me.
After all. there's an argument to be made
that some small part of this is my fault.
I got you covered. Snoopy.
Me too.
We're here for you. Snoopy.
I wouldn't miss it.
You have my scrubber.
All right. all right!
I guess I'll supervise.
No matter where I sleep tonight
Your love is always
Tucking me in tight
Friends are there
To keep you shining bright
Home is where your heart feels light
Some say it's over the rainbow
Deep inside of your dreams
Deep inside your dreams
But lucky for me
I'm where I'm supposed to be
Home where your heart found
Some say it's over the rainbow
Deep inside of your dreams
But lucky for me
I am where I'm supposed to be
Home where your heart found me
Welcome home. Snoopy.
Don't forget. we're in this together.
This wasn't exactly
what I meant by together.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today